# Javier Ricardo Fernández Molinari

Web Developer

La Plata, Argentina (UTC-3)

(+54) 9 1123860954

jadosfer @hotmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/javier-fernandez
molinari/

Portfolio: https://jadosfer.github.io/Portfolio-JFM/

https://github.com/jadosfer

Dev Full Stack SSr. at AFIP with 3 years of experience in Angular/VUE/JAVA.

My first serious project was the development of a web app for a company that distributes protein products, fat burners, recuperators, and others. The application allows you to carry information on orders, products, customers, vendors, stock, vendor commissions, and so on. I developed it using angular 11 and firebase.

My next work experience was for a government agency, where I participated on the front-end of an application to invoice sales in an agile way. I developed some screens using vue3.

Besides, in the same agency I'm currently participating in the development of a web app for inquiries and requests for procedures, regarding the issuance of receipts. I have developed several screens on the front-end using vue2 and I have developed a large part of the server side using Java 8.

I have 1 year of experience using Scrum, and 3 years using git/github/gitlab.

In this job I look for improve my skills and to learn the best practices in developing programs.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

AFIP - Administración Federal de Ingresos Públicos,

#### Habilitación de comprobantes— January, 2022 - Present

- Development of a web app for inquiries and requests for procedures, regarding the issuance of receipts.
- Design and Develop on both, client and server sides.

Tech Stack: vue 2 and Java 1.8 + Springboot + Hibernate

#### Facturador Simplificado — September, 2021 - December, 2021

• Developed of some screens on the Front-End of a web app to invoice sales in an easy and fast way.

Tech Stack: vue 3 and Java 1.8 + Springboot + Hibernate

## Gentech Mar del Plata (Freelancer) — August, 2019 - Present

- Full design and develop of an e-commerce platform for a local company.
- The company currently uses the app and often asks for more functionalities.
- https://github.com/jadosfer/Distribuidora

Tech Stack: Angular 11/12 and firebase.

### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: <a href="Intermediate">Intermediate</a>: JavaScript, Java, C#.</a>
Frameworks Tools: <a href="Intermediate">Intermediate</a>: Angular, VUE <a href="Basic">Basic</a>: Springboot.</a>
Data Base: <a href="Intermediate">Intermediate</a>: SQL SERVER, MYSQL, POSTGRESQL, ORACLE.

**Tools:** Git, Github, Gitlab, Angular Material 7, Adobe XD.

Agile: Scrum.

Languages: Advanced: English; Native: Spanish.

## **EDUCATION**

National University of Mar del Plata - Mar del Plata, Buenos Aires. Electronic Engineering, April 2005.